let questions = [{

    numb: 1,
    question: "In the UK, the abbreviation NHS stands for National what Service?",
    answer: "B. Health",
    options: [
        "A. Humanity",
        "B. Health",
        "C. Honour",
        "D. Household",
    ]
},  
{
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which Disney character famously leaves a glass slipper behind at a royal ball?",
    answer: "C. Cinderella",
    options: [
        "A. Pocahontas",
        "B. Sleeping Beauty",
        "C. Cinderella",
        "D. Elsa",
             ]
},  
{
    numb: 3,
    question: "Who was the youngest British Prime Minister?",
    answer: "B. William Pitt the Yonger",
    options: [
        "A. David Cameron",
        "B. William Pitt the Yonger",
        "C. Tony Blair",
        "D. William Cavendish",
            ]
},  
{ 
    numb: 4,
    question: "Who won the first ever football World Cup?",
    answer: "A. Uruguay" ,
    options: [
        "A. Uruguay" ,
        "B. Brazil",
        "C. Portugal",
        "D. Sweden",
            ]
},
{  
    numb: 5,
    question: "What was the only painting sold by Vincent van Gogh during his lifetime?",
    answer: "C. The Red Vineyard",
    options: [
        "A. Sunflowers",
        "B. The Starry Night",
        "C. The Red Vineyard",
        "D. The Yellow House",
          ]
},  
{  
    numb: 6,
    question: "How many million miles away is the sun from the Earth?",
    answer:  "A. 93 million",
    options: [
        "A. 93 million",
        "B. 12 million",
        "C. 136 million",
        "D. 200 million",
            ]
},  
{
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which singer has a tattoo of Heinz tomato ketchup on his arm?",
    answer:  "D. Ed Sheeran",
    options: [
        "A. Lewis Capaldi",
        "B. Martin Kemp",
        "C. Tom Jones",
        "D. Ed Sheeran",
           ]
 },
 {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Duroc, Berkshire and Mangalica are breeds of which farmyard animal?",
    answer:  "C. Pig",
    options: [
         "A. Chicken",
         "B. Cow",
         "C. Pig",
         "D. Sheep",
            ]
 }, 
 { 
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which city will host the 2028 Olympic Games?",
    answer:  "D. Los Angeles",
    options: [
        "A. Beijing",
        "B. Paris",
        "C. Tokyo",
        "D. Los Angeles",
            ]
},
{  
    numb: 10,
    question: "In the UK, the abbreviation NHS stands for National what Service?",
    answer: "B. Health",
    options: [
        "A. Humanity",
        "B. Health",
        "C. Honour",
        "D. Household",
            ]
 },
{  
    numb: 11,
    question: "What is the most sold flavour of Walkerâ€™s crisps?",
    answer: "A. Cheese and Onion",
    options: [
        "A. Cheese and Onion",
        "B. Salted and Vinegar",
        "C. Prawn Cocktail",
        "D. Ready Salted",
           ]
 },
 {  
    numb: 12,
    question: "What colour were the Pyramids of Giza originally?",
    answer: "D. White",
    options: [
         "A. Orange",
         "B. Blue",
         "C. Pink",
         "D. White",
          ]
 },  

 ]